[{"answer": "Well, there are.", "docId": "130502pmt", "aSentId": 29, "question": "What can you tell me about that part of it?", "qSentId": 28}, {"answer": "Well, that is one of the possibilities.", "docId": "130502pmt", "aSentId": 37, "question": "I believe we're working on the assumption that it's by the Tsarnaev family, possibly an uncle, is that right?", "qSentId": 36}, {"answer": "Well, first of all, it certainly could be what you described.", "docId": "130502pmt", "aSentId": 56, "question": "Or do you fear it's something linked to Dagestan, to extremists in a wider circle of dangerous people?", "qSentId": 55}, {"answer": "Well, very difficult.", "docId": "130502pmt", "aSentId": 71, "question": "How do you deal with this new menace of young people who haven't picked up on many radars before, doing this kind of thing?", "qSentId": 70}, {"answer": "I think at least to a limited degree that the criticism is warranted.", "docId": "130502pmt", "aSentId": 81, "question": "Do you think they're right to level that kind of criticism?", "qSentId": 80}, {"answer": "My personal opinion, yes.", "docId": "130502pmt", "aSentId": 93, "question": "Is that a good move for America, do you think, to do something of that nature?", "qSentId": 92}, {"answer": "I don't know if he would have to do something.", "docId": "130502pmt", "aSentId": 110, "question": "But if it turns out there is unequivocal evidence of sarin use, that they have used weapons of mass destruction, chemical weapons and so on, Obama, having said that that's the red line, would have to do something, wouldn't he?", "qSentId": 109}, {"answer": "Well, I don't have much experience with fire.", "docId": "130502pmt", "aSentId": 145, "question": "Or do you feel like they're getting it under control?", "qSentId": 144}, {"answer": "If you're asking me what's going on surrounding, the wind I know has been somewhat swirling today.", "docId": "130502pmt", "aSentId": 162, "question": "Or is there a fear that other houses are coming into its radar?", "qSentId": 161}, {"answer": "At the time I did.", "docId": "130502pmt", "aSentId": 227, "question": "I mean, do you believe that?", "qSentId": 226}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "130502pmt", "aSentId": 232, "question": "Now that she's turned up alive, do you know what the legal position is with your second marriage?", "qSentId": 231}, {"answer": "As of right now I don't.", "docId": "130502pmt", "aSentId": 248, "question": "I mean, do you -- do you want to see her?", "qSentId": 247}, {"answer": ".", "docId": "130502pmt", "aSentId": 254, "question": "What does that make you feel?", "qSentId": 253}, {"answer": "It's definitely hard.", "docId": "130502pmt", "aSentId": 275, "question": "Morgan, what was your reaction when you saw the new picture of your mother?", "qSentId": 274}, {"answer": "I hope to eventually forgive her one day for myself, not for her.", "docId": "130502pmt", "aSentId": 283, "question": "Or do you think it's beyond any redemption or apology?", "qSentId": 282}, {"answer": "I was really shocked.", "docId": "130502pmt", "aSentId": 289, "question": "How did you feel when you heard what had happened?", "qSentId": 288}, {"answer": ".", "docId": "130502pmt", "aSentId": 295, "question": "How would you feel about that?", "qSentId": 294}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "130502pmt", "aSentId": 320, "question": "I'm now being arrested and handcuffed?", "qSentId": 319}, {"answer": "I don't need to know your name.", "docId": "130502pmt", "aSentId": 322, "question": "Do you know my name, sir?", "qSentId": 321}, {"answer": "Not quite yet.", "docId": "130502pmt", "aSentId": 324, "question": "You don't need to know my name?", "qSentId": 323}, {"answer": "The marketing is directed at the parents, obviously.", "docId": "130502pmt", "aSentId": 364, "question": "What is your view?", "qSentId": 363}, {"answer": "I think that there's an argument to be made in favor of that.", "docId": "130502pmt", "aSentId": 385, "question": "Should it be banned, that kind of advertising?", "qSentId": 384}, {"answer": "We can.", "docId": "130502pmt", "aSentId": 395, "question": "We should focus on the central problem then?", "qSentId": 394}, {"answer": "I'm fairly certain the liability law already covers a lot of this.", "docId": "130502pmt", "aSentId": 398, "question": "But you agree with me, then, that you would bring in a form of gun control, which would be prohibiting companies like Crickett from targeting young people with guns?", "qSentId": 397}, {"answer": "Well, they're not effective, unfortunately.", "docId": "130502pmt", "aSentId": 407, "question": "What is going on?", "qSentId": 406}, {"answer": "Because that is the fundamental basis of American freedom.", "docId": "130502pmt", "aSentId": 420, "question": "Why?", "qSentId": 419}, {"answer": "The tyranny would come from the government.", "docId": "130502pmt", "aSentId": 423, "question": "Where would the tyranny come from?", "qSentId": 422}, {"answer": "No, not Barack Obama's government.", "docId": "130502pmt", "aSentId": 425, "question": "Barack Obama's government?", "qSentId": 424}, {"answer": "I couldn't name you a name.", "docId": "130502pmt", "aSentId": 428, "question": "So whose government?", "qSentId": 427}, {"answer": "I don't believe in the next few years.", "docId": "130502pmt", "aSentId": 431, "question": "You personally believe, like a third of these people, that you will need in the next few years, it says -- you will need to have weapons to take on your own government?", "qSentId": 430}, {"answer": "We've discussed this.", "docId": "130502pmt", "aSentId": 452, "question": "Why don't we just go with a full gun ban?", "qSentId": 451}, {"answer": "I don't think it's a cheap shot.", "docId": "130502pmt", "aSentId": 466, "question": "What such a cheap shot against a guy who did a pretty brave thing?", "qSentId": 465}, {"answer": "I don't understand why --", "docId": "130502pmt", "aSentId": 479, "question": "I think you may be homophobic simply because you said why is Jason Collins a hero because he's gay?", "qSentId": 478}, {"answer": "I'm not sneering at him --", "docId": "130502pmt", "aSentId": 481, "question": "Why sneer at a guy for coming out?", "qSentId": 480}, {"answer": "I don't think it's homophobic to simply say we're apathetic about people's personal lives.", "docId": "130502pmt", "aSentId": 483, "question": "-- one thing homophobic?", "qSentId": 482}, {"answer": "Got to leave it there, but come off it.", "docId": "130502pmt", "aSentId": 507, "question": "Come off it?", "qSentId": 506}, {"answer": "Ben Shapiro, come back soon on the Grill there, and well roasted he was, too.", "docId": "130502pmt", "aSentId": 522, "question": "Why is it a big deal?", "qSentId": 521}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "130502pmt", "aSentId": 537, "question": "I'm now being arrested and handcuffed?", "qSentId": 536}, {"answer": "I don't need to know your name.", "docId": "130502pmt", "aSentId": 539, "question": "Do you know my name, sir?", "qSentId": 538}, {"answer": "Not quite yet.", "docId": "130502pmt", "aSentId": 541, "question": "You don't need to know my name?", "qSentId": 540}, {"answer": "Well, we've seen Reese Witherspoon taking on these kind of darker rolls, this much more complicated roll in \"Mud,\" which came out last weekend.", "docId": "130502pmt", "aSentId": 549, "question": "How bad is this for Reese Witherspoon?", "qSentId": 548}, {"answer": "She has got to be so humiliated.", "docId": "130502pmt", "aSentId": 563, "question": "Abby, sincere enough for you?", "qSentId": 562}, {"answer": "It's easy.", "docId": "130502pmt", "aSentId": 590, "question": "I don't think I can do this?", "qSentId": 589}, {"answer": "I'm going to go with racist for 500, Alex. Here's the thing, it can be satirical, it can be witty and it can be edgy.", "docId": "130502pmt", "aSentId": 599, "question": "Or was it just plain offensive?", "qSentId": 598}, {"answer": "I was saying, it's completely misogynistic as well.", "docId": "130502pmt", "aSentId": 614, "question": "Abby, you go?", "qSentId": 613}, {"answer": "I think the fact that we're even talking about this illustrates that it may have very well been meant to just go viral and be pulled.", "docId": "130502pmt", "aSentId": 623, "question": "Maeve, you're as incensed as Abby?", "qSentId": 622}, {"answer": "The other thing we're talking about today is Mitt Romney has made this commencement speech today.", "docId": "130502pmt", "aSentId": 628, "question": "Why else would we be talking about Mountain Dew, right?", "qSentId": 627}, {"answer": "I think we are just seeing the real Mitt Romney emerge.", "docId": "130502pmt", "aSentId": 653, "question": "Is it a good idea for women to have lots of kids very quickly and then go off and do what they want to do?", "qSentId": 652}, {"answer": "This is the Mitt Romney that I didn't want to vote for and that I didn't vote for.", "docId": "130502pmt", "aSentId": 659, "question": "Marc, final word from you?", "qSentId": 658}]